<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Associated Press News: Breaking News, Latest Headlines and Videos</title>
    <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
    <description>Read the latest headlines, breaking news, and videos at APNews.com, the definitive source for independent journalism from every corner of the globe.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:30:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://apnews.com/index.rss" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" />
    <item>
      <title>Rare tornado hits Haiti, injuring more than 50 people and leaving hundreds homeless</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/haiti-tornado-injured-a0c39075d159889e7259e04c2e338c34</link>
      <description>A rare tornado in northern Haiti has injured more than 50 people and destroyed more than 200 homes. The U.N.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:30:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/haiti-tornado-injured-a0c39075d159889e7259e04c2e338c34</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egyptians accused in deadly shipwreck released from Greek jail after court dismissed the case</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/migration-greece-egyptians-released-trawler-sinking-3533ca9d3ab8d851c790f7cde87e053a</link>
      <description>A group of Egyptians jailed for nearly a year pending trial for a deadly shipwreck have been released from jail in southern Greece, a day after a Greek court threw out the case against them on grounds that it had no jurisdiction to try it.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/migration-greece-egyptians-released-trawler-sinking-3533ca9d3ab8d851c790f7cde87e053a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Review: Lenny Kravitz leans on the funk with glorious 'Blue Electric Light'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lenny-kravitz-electric-light-167560b9c723af05ecef49b101759d4a</link>
      <description>The bass is banging, the guitars are shrieking and Lenny Kravitz is howling on “Blue Electric Light,” the rocker’s best stuff in years, offering a welcome blast of funk in 2024.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:25:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/lenny-kravitz-electric-light-167560b9c723af05ecef49b101759d4a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private investment firms partner to potentially cash in following sweeping changes in college sports</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/collegiate-athletic-solution-private-equity-46ee075d884689d2942f70077eee463a</link>
      <description>Two private investment firms have created a platform to help athletic departments find funding with college sports on the verge of sweeping change that could have long-term financial implications.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:22:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/collegiate-athletic-solution-private-equity-46ee075d884689d2942f70077eee463a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican James Comer and progressive Katie Porter push overhaul of presidential ethics rules</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/congress-presidential-ethics-transparency-trump-biden-emoluments-6dd35259c5b5f99dd56d006c9fa05536</link>
      <description>Bipartisan legislation introduced in the House would require presidents and vice presidents to publicly disclose tax returns before, during and after their time in the White House.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:13:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/congress-presidential-ethics-transparency-trump-biden-emoluments-6dd35259c5b5f99dd56d006c9fa05536</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCLA police chief reassigned following criticism over handling of campus demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ucla-police-chief-campus-protests-israel-palestinians-432b22d5aba4ce44794ab3d2826fa20d</link>
      <description>The police chief at the University of California, Los Angeles, has been reassigned amid criticism of his handling of campus demonstrations.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:11:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/ucla-police-chief-campus-protests-israel-palestinians-432b22d5aba4ce44794ab3d2826fa20d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana governor declares emergency after severe storms leave 3 dead</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/louisiana-storms-state-of-emergency-7f978e915d972e21864b94898eab01cf</link>
      <description>A state of emergency has been ordered after severe storms swept Louisiana last week, knocking out power to nearly 160,000 people and leaving three dead, including a pregnant woman and her unborn child.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:10:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/louisiana-storms-state-of-emergency-7f978e915d972e21864b94898eab01cf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Murray receives wild card to play doubles at French Open with Daniel Evans</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tennis-french-open-murray-doubles-25e017266056ce262d8cdbeb07d13ea0</link>
      <description>Three-time Grand Slam champion Andy Murray and Daniel Evans have been granted a wild card to play together in doubles at the French Open.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:06:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/tennis-french-open-murray-doubles-25e017266056ce262d8cdbeb07d13ea0</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Latest | Spain, Ireland and Norway make a coordinated move to recognize a Palestinian state</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/world-news/palestinian-territories-government-spain-israel-hamas-war-israel-israel-government-7772b128e634e3e28e4bafb1663d7d81</link>
      <description>Norway, Ireland and Spain have recognized a Palestinian state, a move welcomed by Palestinians as an affirmation of their decadeslong quest while Israel recalled its ambassadors to the three countries.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:05:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/world-news/palestinian-territories-government-spain-israel-hamas-war-israel-israel-government-7772b128e634e3e28e4bafb1663d7d81</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity labeling for smart devices aims to help people choose items less likely to be hacked</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cybersecurity-google-samsung-amazon-cyber-trust-e5f0ab2a207e556190e189dbb27c7b71</link>
      <description>Smart devices like baby monitors, fitness trackers and internet-connected appliances will soon be eligible for labels certifying that they meet federal cybersecurity standards.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:49:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/cybersecurity-google-samsung-amazon-cyber-trust-e5f0ab2a207e556190e189dbb27c7b71</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 'embarrassing' Indy 500, Rahal Letterman Lanigan is still searching for speed at the Brickyard</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/indianapolis-500-rahal-letterman-lanigan-141d9e38a5338d7c95ef1c070ef6c600</link>
      <description>Graham Rahal felt better about the direction Rahal Letterman Lanigan was headed this year after failing to qualify his own car for the Indianapolis 500 last May.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/indianapolis-500-rahal-letterman-lanigan-141d9e38a5338d7c95ef1c070ef6c600</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A UK election has been called for July 4. Here's what to know</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/uk-britain-election-sunak-starmer-conservatives-labour-0daef4ea348f58adcb889874692fa0d9</link>
      <description>The United Kingdom will hold its first election in five years in a country reeling from the cost-of-living crisis, the fallout from Israel-Hamas conflict and deep divisions over how to deal with migrants and asylum seekers crossing the English Channel from Europe on small inflatable boats.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:28:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/uk-britain-election-sunak-starmer-conservatives-labour-0daef4ea348f58adcb889874692fa0d9</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feaster is honored by SC Athletic Hall and now is focused on seeing daughter Strong play at UConn</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/allison-feaster-sarah-strong-sc-hall-of-fame-a72ce76cf40957ab34cdb9e4e4f68949</link>
      <description>Allison Feaster has a career's worth of basketball milestones, which is why she was honored this week with enshrinement into the South Carolina Athletic Hall of Fame.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:23:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/allison-feaster-sarah-strong-sc-hall-of-fame-a72ce76cf40957ab34cdb9e4e4f68949</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICC prosecutor's warrant requests for Israel and Hamas leaders ignite debate about court's role</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/icc-israel-hamas-gaza-warrants-court-c0509ed7daf21f9cc78ec17b8e627327</link>
      <description>Prosecutor Karim Khan has broken new ground with his stunning announcement that he had requested arrest warrants for Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, his defense minister and the leaders of Hamas on charges of war crimes and crimes against humanity.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:21:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/icc-israel-hamas-gaza-warrants-court-c0509ed7daf21f9cc78ec17b8e627327</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target, Lululemon fall; Petco, Dycom rise, Wednesday, 5/22/2024</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-stocks-wall-street-815c0b94e3fcdf46e0b5e7f6a82de60c</link>
      <description>Stocks that are trading heavily or have substantial price changes on Wednesday: Target, Lululemon fall; Petco, Dycom.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:20:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-stocks-wall-street-815c0b94e3fcdf46e0b5e7f6a82de60c</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC to consider rules for AI-generated political ads on TV and radio, but can't touch streaming</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-political-ads-fcc-f42380ea8f984e81a622f0f3db3224a6</link>
      <description>The nation’s top telecommunications regulator is introducing a proposal to require political advertisers to disclose when they use content generated by artificial intelligence in broadcast TV and radio ads.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:06:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/artificial-intelligence-political-ads-fcc-f42380ea8f984e81a622f0f3db3224a6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh and the Steelers will be hosting the 2026 NFL draft</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-draft-pittsburgh-2026-0fdac7e23a3ca27b64d83a8173baaa72</link>
      <description>The NFL has awarded the 2026 draft to Pittsburgh with the Steelers ready to tap Pennsylvania’s deep football tradition trying to meet the new standard for host cities.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-draft-pittsburgh-2026-0fdac7e23a3ca27b64d83a8173baaa72</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steinhauser soloes to first pro win in Stage 17, Pogacar extends Giro lead to nearly eight minutes</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/giro-pogacar-steinhauser-stage-17-5a819c31993d3ebf275ff64c456387e1</link>
      <description>Georg Steinhauser soloed to his first professional victory in the brutal 17th stage of the Giro d’Italia and overall leader Tadej Pogacar extended his already considerable advantage to nearly eight minutes.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/giro-pogacar-steinhauser-stage-17-5a819c31993d3ebf275ff64c456387e1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee to become first state to offer free diapers for Medicaid families</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tennessee-free-diapers-medicaid-fa94094385a4ae276acc945ab8dbb7c0</link>
      <description>Tennessee will soon become the first state in the country to offer free diapers to families enrolled in the state’s Medicaid program after receiving federal approval, state officials have confirmed.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/tennessee-free-diapers-medicaid-fa94094385a4ae276acc945ab8dbb7c0</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China sanctions US defense-related companies and executives over Russia, Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-taiwan-russia-ukraine-sanctions-98b8d3e3ecaf8603e91bac7c5f9388c7</link>
      <description>China has sanctioned 12 defense-related U.S. companies and 10 executives over arms sales to Taiwan and to retaliate for earlier American sanctions on Chinese companies tied to Russia.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:59:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/china-taiwan-russia-ukraine-sanctions-98b8d3e3ecaf8603e91bac7c5f9388c7</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dumping oil at sea leads to $2 million fine for shipping companies</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oil-dumping-federal-charges-a616098d0968bfaf84d7909ea42b3124</link>
      <description>Two shipping companies agreed to pay $2 million in penalties after pleading guilty to federal charges related to the dumping of oil in the Atlantic Ocean by a ship bound for New Orleans.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:59:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/oil-dumping-federal-charges-a616098d0968bfaf84d7909ea42b3124</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirming 200th judge under Biden as Democrats surpass Trump's pace</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-judges-trump-senate-200-confirmed-63b764d071d9c084b6669eabab527240</link>
      <description>The Senate has confirmed the 200th federal judge of President Joe Biden’s tenure. That's about a month earlier than Donald Trump hit the 200 mark in his term.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/biden-judges-trump-senate-200-confirmed-63b764d071d9c084b6669eabab527240</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge: 66 abused as children in Pennsylvania juvenile facilities</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pennsylvania-juvenile-sexual-abuse-c3b71f64f522b94ff1b542686d2bdbd6</link>
      <description>The lawsuits describe how 66 people, now adults, say they were victimized by guards, nurses, supervisors and others.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/pennsylvania-juvenile-sexual-abuse-c3b71f64f522b94ff1b542686d2bdbd6</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former UMA presidential candidate has been paid more than $370K under settlement</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/uma-university-president-payments-maine-8a72be0212bc88a949100c42338be495</link>
      <description>The former incoming president of the University of Maine at Augusta who withdrew amid complaints from faculty members in 2022 is still collecting about $20,000 a month from the state university system.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:21:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/uma-university-president-payments-maine-8a72be0212bc88a949100c42338be495</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clark, Reese and Brink have already been a huge boon for WNBA with high attendance and ratings</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wnba-clark-reese-ratings-7d8f877aa1dfc8710da36476f8627a25</link>
      <description>Fueled by its sensational rookie class of Caitlin Clark, Angel Reese and Cameron Brink, the WNBA had a huge first week in terms of attendance, ratings and digital media.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:16:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/wnba-clark-reese-ratings-7d8f877aa1dfc8710da36476f8627a25</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to spend billions on a flood-prone East Texas highway may not solve the problem</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/highway-59-upgrades-evacuation-route-flooding-17bcc1e209ee4ccf942aa91134edb51a</link>
      <description>Plans to upgrade a major evacuation route from Houston are moving forward, but Texas Department of Transportation officials say there's no guarantee that the project will fix flooding problems.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:06:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/highway-59-upgrades-evacuation-route-flooding-17bcc1e209ee4ccf942aa91134edb51a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brunson has surgery to repair broken left hand, and Knicks say Bogdanovic also underwent procedure</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/knicks-brunson-surgery-bogdanovic-0531e66d9e792948fa916795dc374aae</link>
      <description>Jalen Brunson has had surgery to repair the broken left hand he sustained while the New York Knicks were losing Game 7 of the Eastern Conference semifinals.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/knicks-brunson-surgery-bogdanovic-0531e66d9e792948fa916795dc374aae</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of Wegovy and other weight-loss drugs soars among kids and young adults</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wegovy-ozempic-teens-young-adults-24047516e0c3b4f678c3e91f4ed6face</link>
      <description>Use of diabetes and obesity medications such as Ozempic, Wegovy and other so-called GLP-1 drugs has soared among teens and young adults.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/wegovy-ozempic-teens-young-adults-24047516e0c3b4f678c3e91f4ed6face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Pidgeon finds her voice, her inner rock god and a Tony nomination in Broadway's 'Stereophonic'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sarah-pidgeon-stereophonic-tony-ec3e50a370df23a65591f37158cb1486</link>
      <description>Sarah Pidgeon is making her Broadway debut this season in a celebrated, thoughtful show about how art is created. And getting her first Tony Award nomination.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/sarah-pidgeon-stereophonic-tony-ec3e50a370df23a65591f37158cb1486</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right party bans its top European election candidate from campaigning after Nazi remark</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/germany-afd-krah-nazi-2c3b1537d02622a9948933c18c14dd51</link>
      <description>Germany’s far-right Alternative for Germany party has banned its top candidate for next month’s European election from making any more campaign appearances and said he would resign from the party’s board immediately.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:48:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://apnews.com/article/germany-afd-krah-nazi-2c3b1537d02622a9948933c18c14dd51</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

